Guide to the Peter Goin photographs, 1987-2006 and undated RL.00459
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Papers, 1987-2006 and undated; 1 folders
  - Correspondence, 1991-1999, 1
    - Duke University Library, 1991-1999 (Box 7)
      Regarding the transfer of Goin archives to the library.
    - Writers, 1991-1993 (Box 7)
    - Research, 1992-1993 (Box 7)
    - Publishers, 1993 (Box 7)
    - Exhibitions, 1992-1996 (Box 7)
    - Image acquisition, 1992 (Box 7)
  - Conferences, 1993-1994 and undated, 2
    - National Interagency Wildlife Conference, 1993 (Box 7)
    - Association of American Geographers, 1994; 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Lecture notes, undated (Box 7)
  - Manuscript materials for Humanature, 1991-1995 and undated, 3
    - Outline, 1991 (Box 7)
    - Captions, undated (Box 7)
    - Draft excerpt, 1994-1995 (Box 7)
    - Reader comments, 1992 (Box 7)
    - Reader reports, 1994-1995 (Box 7)
  - Research, 1988-2006 and undated, 4
    - Photocopied articles from books and journals, undated (Box 7)
    - Articles from magazines, 1991-1996 (Box 7)
    - Articles and clippings from newspapers, 1992-2006 (Box 7)
    - Pamphlets, 1990 and undated (Box 7)
    - Cabrillo National Monument, 1993 (Box 7)
    - Carnivore Preservation Trust, 1990s (Box 7)
    - Channel Islands National Park, 1993 (Box 7)
    - Conservation and Research Center, National Zoo, 1991-1995 (Box 7)
    - Duke Power, 1991 (Box 7)
    - Eric Katz conference papers, 1990-1992 (Box 7)
    - Grand Canyon, 1993 (Box 7)
    - H. J. Andrews Experimental Forest, 1992 (Box 7)
    - Kissimmee River, 1991-1992; 4 folders (Box 7)
      Includes Environmental Restoration report by the US Army Corps of Engineers, 1991, and Alternative Plan Evaluation and Preliminary Design Report by the South Florida Water Management District, 1990.
    - Kudzu, 1992 (Box 7)
    - Maps, 1990s; 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Nature conservancy, 1988-1991 (Box 7)
    - Notes, 1990s; 3 folders (Box 7)
    - North Carolina Zoological Park, 1992-1999 (Box 7)
    - Peachtree Rock Preserve, 1992 (Box 7)
    - Savannah River Site, 1992 (Box 7)
    - Virginia Beach, 1992 (Box 7, Oversize-folder 1)
  - Travelling exhibit, 1987-2001, 5
    - Acceptances, 1997-1998 (Box 7)
    - Rejections, 1987-2001, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - University of Texas Press, 1994-1995, 6
    - Miscellaneous publication/press materials, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Publicity for Humanature, 1996-1998
    - Publicity folder (Box 8)